Patrick R. Ceriale

(805) 453-2264 | Patceriale@gmail.com | Seattle, Washington

GitHub: http://bit.ly/cerialegit | LinkedIn: http://bit.ly/cerialeli

Portfolio: www.patrickceriale.me/

Patrick is a Seattle-based Full-stack developer with experience in the full range of applications from creating dynamic user interfaces to RESTful APIs. He particularly enjoys the creative aspect of Front-end development and has a passion for building innovative and beautiful applications in a team environment. He shows strength in problem solving, team collaboration, and attention to detail.

Technical Skills:

React.js, Angular, Vue.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, Azure, HTML/CSS, jQuery, Express.js, Node.js, SQL/NoSQL Databases, GitHub, Azure DevOps, Rest APIs, Microsoft Power Platform, Microsoft 365, Agile Team Practices, Design & Build Enablement

Projects:

<u>Government Organization</u> – Avanade Full-stack Developer, Consultant Relevant Tech: JavaScript, ReactJS, HTML/CSS, Modern SharePoint, Azure Devops

- Updated a government employee intranet to Modern SharePoint with custom React webparts. Enabled employees to consolidate multiple sources into central hub, allowing easier access to important information from one location
- Integrated React apps to client's SharePoint tenant, allowing users to consume data queried from the client Azure Active Directory, SharePoint lists and thirdparty APIs.
- Collaborated with SharePoint Architect to create efficient React webparts, according to the client's requirements
- Conducted live demos with client, answering questions regarding development and easing any production concerns

<u>Multinational Technology Corporation</u> – Avanade Full-Stack Developer, Consultant Relevant Tech: JavaScript, Elixir/Phoenix, Azure Devops, RESTful APIs

- Updated a multinational tech corporation's application to function more efficiently and accurately using the client's obscure tech stack: Elixir and Phoenix
- Implemented web sockets, allowing for a more logical approach to client-server communication
- Enabled client use data collection using New Relic, granting optimization at high traffic times

<u>Healthcare Organization</u> – Avanade User Experience Engineer, Consultant Relevant Tech: JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Microsoft Power Platform, Microsoft Dynamics

 Accountable for prototype work and other software engineering solutions that created optimized user experience Translated design concepts to prototype solutions as quickly and tangibly as possible, with a balanced understanding of technical feasibility implications and design intent.

Relevant Work Experience:

Full-Stack Developer - Avanade

April 2021 - Present

- Drive the delivery of front-end development, user experience and deep back-end integrations for digital products and services
- Work in an agile and lean environment to build new digital solutions for clients throughout a variety of technology stacks
- Collaborate with developers, testers, and the scrum master to build new, wellcrafted software and digital experiences

Production Manager - Urban Family Brewing Company May 2018 - July 2020

- Responsible for inception, execution, and delivery of products to delight customers, maximize efficiency and minimize loss
- Learned the mechanics of brewing equipment for installation, maintenance, and repairs
- Devised and implemented system to record inventories and perform cost analysis of beers

Specialty Brewer - Telegraph Brewing Company

May 2015 – March 2018

- · Designed and brewed all recipes for the barrel-aged and specialty beer
- Presented at symposiums and workshops on brewing processes, techniques, and ideology

Education & Certifications:

California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo

Bachelor of Science in Biology Date of graduation: June 9, 2012

University of Washington, Seattle

Full Stack Coding Boot Camp Date of completion: November 24, 2020

AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

Self-taught course Date of completion: June 17, 2021

PL-900: Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals

Self-taught course Date of completion: August 25, 2022